lexusownersclub.com 2011-12-26

# Lexus Owners Club USA

**THE OWNERS CLUB PRIVACY POLICY**

The Owners Club respects your privacy and is committed to protect the personal information that you share with us. Generally, you can browse through our website without giving us any information about yourself. When we do need your personal information to provide services that you request or when you choose to provide us with your personal information, this policy describes how we collect and use your personal information.

 **Information Collection**

Personal information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, email address, a home, postal or other physical address, other contact information, title, birth date, gender, occupation, industry, personal interests, other information when needed to provide a service you requested.

When you browse our website, you do so anonymously, unless you have previously indicated that you wish the Owners Club to remember your login and password. We don't automatically collect personal information, including your email address. We do log your IP address (the Internet address /liof your computer) to give us an idea of which part of our website you visit and how long you spend there. But we do not link your IP address to any personal information unless you have logged in to our website. Like many other commercial websites, The Owners Club website may use a standard technology called a "cookie" to collect information about how you use the site. Please go to "Cookies and Tracking Information" below for more information.

 **How We Use Information Collected**

The Owners Club uses information for several general purposes: to personalize your experience on our website, to keep you up to date on the latest The Owners Club announcements, special offers or other information we think you'd like to hear about from us, and to better understand your needs and provide you with better services. This is essential to keeping our service free.

We do not share information about individual users in any circumstances.

 **Cookies and Tracking Technology**

A cookie is a small data file that certain Web sites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that the site uses to track the pages you've visited, but the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. Some parts of The Owners Club's website use cookies to track user traffic patterns. We do this in order to determine the usefulness of our website information to our users and to see how effective our navigational structure is in helping users reach that information.

If you prefer not to receive cookies while browsing our website, you can set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies and refuse the cookie when your browser alerts you to its presence. You can also refuse all cookies by turning them off in your browser, although you may not be able to take full advantage of The Owners Club's website if you do so. In particular, you may be required to accept cookies in order to complete certain actions on our website. You do not need to have cookies turned on, however, to use/navigate through many parts of our website, except access to certain of The Owners Club's web pages may require a login and password.

 **Data Security**

Your The Owners Club account information is password-protected for your privacy and security. The Owners Club safeguards the security of the data you send us with physical, electronic, and managerial procedures. While we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure the security of the information you transmit to us, and so we urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. Change your passwords often, use a combination of letters and numbers, and make sure you use a secure browser.

 **Children and Privacy**

Our websites do not target and are not intended to attract children under the age of 13. The Owners Club does not knowingly solicit personal information from children under the age of 13 or send them requests for personal information.

 **Third Party Sites**

The Owners Club's website contains links to other sites. The Owners Club does not share your personal information with those websites and is not responsible for their privacy practices. We encourage you to learn about the privacy policies of those companies.

Our website may contain links to websites operated by other companies. Some of these third-party sites may be co-branded with a The Owners Club logo, even though they are not operated or maintained by The Owners Club. Although we choose our business partners carefully, The Owners Club is not responsible for the privacy practices of web sites operated by third parties that are linked to our site. Once you have left our website, you should check the applicable privacy policy of the third party website to determine how they will handle any information they collect from you.  
Changes to this Privacy Policy

The Owners Club will amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will make that information available by posting a notice on this site. ****
